Because it's not a kiss.
キスじゃないから
Make a joke.
シャレをね
You want money, right?
お金欲しいでしょ
Make a joke.
シ ャ レを
He let me check the texture.
質感チェックさせてくれたんです
Oh yeah, look.
そうそう、ほら
Also?
また?
More and more.
どんどん
There's more.
まだある
I don't need money.
お金いらない
good.
いい
You want it, right?
欲しいでしょ
You should just put it in.
入れていけばいいでしょ
Just put it in.
入 れていけばいいで
Sho.
しょ
How's the texture?
質 感どう?
I want to go home.
帰りたいです
No, it's okay.
いやいや、大丈夫
Just a little more.
もうちょっとだけ
I have to check it out.
チェックしないといけない
Yeah, just a little more.
そうそう、もうちょっとだけ
質感
The texture.
質感が
It might be tough.
きつかもね
surely.
確かに
oh yeah.
そうそう
A little lower.
ちょっと下
Get it down.
下出して
Show me the bottom.
下見せて
oh yeah.
そうそう
Down.
下
Look, below.
ほら、下
A little bit
ちょっとチ
Check.
ェ ック
It won't end.
終わんないよ
Because it won't end.
終わんないから
You want to go home, right?
帰りたいでしょ
It won't end if you don't check it.
チェックしないと終わんないんだよ
amazing.
すごい
wait a minute.
ちょっと 待って
It won't end if you don't check it.
チェックしないと終わんない
I won't be able to take this home with me anymore.
これもう持って帰れなくなっちゃうよ
That's fine, right?
いいでしょ
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
That's a bit like that.
ちょっとあれだね
Sorry for a moment.
ちょっとごめん
I'll have to observe it a little more.
もうちょっと観察しなきゃいけないから
Just this.
ちょっとこれ
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Hey, this swimsuit.
ちょっとね、この水着の
First of all, it only comes with a swimsuit.
まず水着付しかないから
I usually wear this swimsuit a lot.
普段これ水着多いな
It's a lot.
多 いんだ
Don't you have any luck?
おケケないの?
why?
なんで?
It's true.
本当だ
I don't have any money.
おケケないんだ
That's amazing.
すごいね
It might actually suit you.
確かに似合うかもね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I'll take a picture.
撮っちゃうよね
Shall we just take pictures and be done with it?
撮影だけして終わろう?
Sharen is also served.
シャレンも出す
Sharen too.
シ ャ レ ンもね
Solid.
しっかり
Because this is important.
これ大事だから
I don't even make swimsuits.
水着も作らないから
Please show me well.
しっかり見せてね
Should I leave it there?
置いとこうか
This is it until now.
これ 今までだよね
Take it.
持っとけ
A hat is fine, right?
帽子いいでしょ
Hold your hand a little.
ちょっと手押さえ
A little from behind.
ちょっと手後ろから
It'll be over in a little while.
ちょっとで終わるから
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Sorry.
ごめんね
It'll be over soon.
すぐ終わる
That's amazing.
すごいね
Are you okay.
大丈夫
It'll be over soon.
すぐ終わるからね
I want to see some more.
もうちょっと見たいな
amazing.
すごい
There's a hole.
穴が開いてる
That's amazing.
すごいね
Open it a little.
ちょっと開いて
You want money, right?
お金欲しいでしょ
お 金欲しいでしょ
Is this no good?
これダメ?
Okay.
いいよ
I don't need money.
お金いらないです
Isn't it dangerous?
やばくない?
Okay.
いいよ
I'll have you do some more after that.
その後にもうちょっとやってもらう
yes.
はい
Are you okay.
大丈夫
By receiving it.
受け取るってことで
Just a little bit.
ちょっとじゃあ
bed.
ベッド
Shall we go to bed?
ベッド行く?
what up?
どうした?
Let's go to bed.
ベッド行こう
It's small, isn't it?
狭いでしょ
Oh no.
や だ
It won't end.
終わんないよ
Pull it a little.
ちょっと引っ張って
what?
何?
I won't go.
行かない
let's go.
行こう
Let's go.
行 く よ
Because I'm receiving money.
お金受け取っちゃってるから
Does that mean you're doing more?
それはもっとしてるってこと?
Is that so?
そういうこと?
I'm shy.
恥ずかしがってる
Your face is turning a little red.
ちょっと顔も赤くなってるでしょ
Are you drunk?
酔っぱらった?
Did you get drunk?
酔っぱらっちゃったの?
I need to cool it down.
冷やさないとね
Because I'm receiving money.
お金受け取っちゃってるから
Yeah.
うん
what up?
どうした?
Look at me.
こっち見てってさ
Because I'm receiving money.
お金受け取っちゃってるから
Not enough?
足りない?
Not enough.
足りない
Open, open.
開いて開いて
Not enough?
足りない?
You received the money, right?
お金受け取ったでしょ
You received it, right?
受 け取ったでしょ
受 け取ってたでしょ
Because I have received it.
受け取っちゃってるから
A smile is important, right?
笑顔大事でしょ?
Because I agree.
同意してるから
I agree.
同意してるね
Peace.
ピースして
Do you not like it?
嫌ですか?
Don't like it?
嫌?
You don't like it, do you?
嫌 じゃないでしょ
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
気持ちいい?
Does it feel good?
Show me the water.
水見せて
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Open yours.
自分のもの開いてみて
Why not try opening that resistance yourself?
その抵抗その他自分で開いてみ?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
Aren't you scared?
怖くない?
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
Because it will end.
終わるから
Because it's a part-time job.
バイトだから
Would you like to open it?
開いてみ?
Because it's a part-time job.
バイトだから
A little finger, inside.
ちょっと指、中
check.
チ ェック
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
Because I'm receiving money.
お金受け取ってるから
how much?
いくら?
Isn't it amazing?
すごくない?
You're making a lot of money.
だいぶ稼いでるじゃん
I'm covered in debt.
借金まみれだよ
I'm going in.
入っていく
Awesome, amazing.
すごいすごい
It's wet.
濡れてるじゃん
Are you sleeping?
寝てるの?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
It would be worse not to resist.
抵抗しないほうがすぐ悪い
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's okay, right?
大丈夫でしょ?
I want to go home.
帰りたい
I'll go home.
帰るから
Shall we go home early then?
じゃあ早く帰ろうか
How does it taste?
味どう?
I don't know.
分かんない
Really sleeping.
本当の寝てる
Oh my goodness.
や ばいね
It makes a sound.
音するよ
terrible.
やばい
You're embarrassed about yours, aren't you?
自分ののが恥ずかしいでしょ?
Isn't it delicious?
おいしいでしょ?
Get the money.
お金もらって
Isn't it delicious?
おいしいでしょ?
Have you ever touched it?
触ったことある?
be.
ある
Because I'm receiving money.
お金受け取ってるんだから
Because I have received it.
受け取っちゃってるから
Because I have already received it.
受 け取っちゃってるから
Because I have received it.
受け取っちゃってるから
Have you seen it?
見たことある?
Look, look.
見て見て
You won't know unless you look closely, right?
よく見ないと分かんないでしょ?
be.
ある
Look, look.
見て見て
Don't you see it?
見ない?
Should I take a picture so you can see it clearly?
よく見えるように撮っとくか
Are you okay.
大丈夫
what happened?
どうしたの?
It'll be over soon.
すぐ終わるから
Seriously.
マジで
Should I take a picture so I can see it clearly?
よ く 見 える ように 撮っとくか
It'll be over soon.
すぐ終わる
Really.
本当に
It'll be over really soon.
本当にすぐ終わる
Take a look first.
まず見てみて
yes.
そう
Shall we count?
数えてみようか
Just look.
見るだけ
Come a little closer.
ちょっと近づいて
Have you seen it?
見たことあるでしょ?
Because it's money.
お金分だから
You want to buy it, right?
買いたいでしょ?
Because this is the end.
これで終わるから
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
what?
何?
I'm running away.
逃げてる
Don't run away.
逃げないで
I had to run away.
逃げるのになって
Because everyone is doing it.
みんなやってるから
Everyone is doing it.
み んなやってるんだよ
Is everyone doing it?
み んなやってる?
That's enough.
もういいじゃん
Have you done much?
結構やったことあんの?
Peace.
ピースして
Smile while doing peace.
ピースしながら笑顔で
agree.
同意
If it's not fun, they'll use it.
楽しくないと使ってくれる
It's not forced.
無理やりじゃないから
Peace, peace.
ピースし、ピースし
Smile, smile.
笑顔、笑顔
Because it's not forced.
無理やりじゃないから
That's amazing, that's amazing.
すごいね、すごいね
Wait a minute, taste.
ちょっとじゃあ、味
Shall we taste it?
味わおうか
I need to give it some flavor.
味 を 出してあげないとね
I think I'll stop.
やめような
Hey, Pero.
ちょっと、ペロって
It won't end.
終わんないよ
You want it to end, right?
終わりたいでしょ?
I want it to end.
終わりたいよね
Let out as much as you can, Pero.
出しただけ出して、ペロを
Try it out.
出してみて
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
go?
いく?
No damage yet.
まだダメージないよ
It'll be over really soon.
ほんとすぐ終わる
I'll finish it right away.
すぐ終わらせる
Wait, something?
ちょっとじゃあ、何か
Hey, why don't you sleep for a while?
ちょっとじゃあ、 寝ても?
Look.
見て
hang on.
待って
One more time.
もう一回
Was it delicious?
美味しかった?
Just the pack, just the pack, right?
パックだけ、パックだけでしょ
It's just the pack.
パックだけでしょ
I can go home soon.
もうすぐ帰れる
No way.
やだな
Ssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssss.
すーすーすーすーすー
delicious?
美味しい?
delicious.
美味しい
It's delicious.
美味しいんだ
Okay, okay.
いいよ、いいよ
It's delicious.
美味しいんだって
Do it right here.
ちゃんとこっちにしろ
It's delicious.
う まいじゃん
You put it in.
入れたね
Have you ever entered it?
入れたことある?
be?
ある?
Have you ever been to Chin Chin?
チンチン行ったことある?
be?
ある?
do not have.
ない
Try moving your foot to the left.
足、左行ってみて
There is nothing that isn't there.
ないことない
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼氏いんの?
not present.
いない
Well then, that's fine.
じゃあ、いいじゃん
Shinso enters.
シンソ入ります
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
Just rub.
こするだけ
You'll run away and go in.
逃げて入るでしょ
Let me rub it.
こすらせて
Have you ever done this?
こしたことある?
Let's try reaching out once.
一回手を伸ばしてみよう
It won't rub, it won't rub.
こすれない、こすれない
It has to rub.
こすれなきゃ
I want to call you.
電話したい
mother.
お母さん
Because I can.
できるから
I can't make a phone call without rubbing it.
こすらないと電話できないから
It's not rubbed.
こすれてないよ
Not much.
あ んまり
I need to get my legs together.
足をくっつかないと
Because I can't call.
電話できないから
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
That's scary.
怖いね
It's okay.
よかねえよ
This is a part-time job.
バイトじゃん、これ
But hands are fine.
でも手っていいから
You want to give it to your mother, right?
お母さんにあげたいでしょ
Well then, right away.
じゃあ、すぐ
It will be over in 1 minute.
1分で終わるから
I'm going to sleep.
寝るよ
good
いい
Yo.
よ
It's here, and it's nice.
ここ にあるし、いいよね
Because I agree.
同意してるから
Does that mean you can just sleep like this?
このまま寝ていいってことでしょ?
1 point.
1分
Just one minute is fine, right?
1分だけいいでしょ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Would you like me to look at this?
こっち見てもらう?
Would you like me to take a look at this?
こ っち見てもらう?
Because I'm receiving it.
受け取ってるから
Let's compete.
勝負しようね
This is because I received it.
受け取ってるから、これ
Because I agree.
同意してるから
同 意してるから
It's amazing.
すげえろい
It's so sexy.
めちゃくちゃえろい
Someone who opens their legs?
足開くの人?
It's so sexy.
めちゃくちゃえろい
If you don't watch it, you won't be able to finish unless you get this.
見ないと、これ取れないと終われないから
We also want to give it to you soon.
俺らも早くあげたいから
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Did I mention it felt good?
気持ちいいって言った?
You said it felt good.
気持ちいいって言ったね
I like this too.
これも好きだな
Which one do you like?
どっちが好き?
That's nice.
いいな
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
気持ちいいの?
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
It's not a crime, right?
犯罪じゃないよね?
It's okay.
大丈夫だね
Because I agreed.
同意してたから
It'll be over soon.
すぐ終わる
Well then, I'd like you to come up a little higher next time.
じゃあ、次ちょっと上来てもらおうかな
Where are you going?
どこ行くの?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
It doesn't hurt, right?
痛くないでしょ?
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
That's fine.
いいじゃん
Just keep bending down like this.
このまま腰を落とすだけだ
pain
痛
stomach.
い
self-divided
自 分
Well, if I move, I might go home early.
で さ、動いたら早く帰るかも
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
My voice is coming out, though.
声出てるよ、でも
It feels good, right?
気 持ちいいでしょ?
気持ちいいでしょ?
amazing.
すごい
Be careful.
注意して
I'll take your place.
俺は代わりになるから
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
It hurts.
痛いね
I want to go home.
帰りたい
I want to go home already.
もう、帰りたい
I want to go home.
帰りたい
It never ends.
終わらない
It'll be over soon.
すぐ終わる
すぐ終わるから
I'll go home.
帰るから
Because I can definitely go home.
絶対帰れるから
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
You want to go home, right?
帰 り たいでしょ?